KURT STATHAM

SUMMARY

I have over a decade of experience in the casual game industry, with past roles in engineering, QA, and site production. As a seasoned multitasker and fast learner, I'm seeking to transition into a role where I can develop my coding skills while contributing to a company dedicated to making the world a better place.

EMPLOYMENT

Course Concierge, LLC, Customer Experience/QA Technician, San Diego, CA (Remote)

Aug. 2020 - Current

- Answer user questions about course content (e.g., basic woodworking, guitar technique, and music theory).
- File bug reports and verify bug fixes.
- · QA new site content and functionality.
- Monitor and review Facebook group activity.
- Edit monthly newsletters.
- · Assist customers with technical issues and billing inquiries.
- Review and approve user project submissions.

DEFY Media, Director, Site Production, Los Angeles, CA

Apr. 2017 - Oct. 2018

- Managed all scheduling and production for the Addicting Games and Shockwave websites.
- Reviewed and approved all prospective Shockwave site content.
- Requested and coordinated the addition of additional features to both the customer facing sites and back end services.
- Served as the technical liaison between the site production and engineering teams.
- Successfully built and maintained relationships with a variety of content providers.
- Identified and remedied any production-related site issues, improving customer experience.
- Trained and mentored junior staff.

Nickelodeon/DEFY Media, Game Release Engineer, Los Angeles, CA

July 2011 - Mar. 2017

- Produced and tested games for the Addicting Games and Shockwave websites.
- Authored content for Shockwave's most popular game, "The Daily Jigsaw".
- Maintained and improved legacy production systems.
- Wrote scripts to automate and streamline game production.
- Assisted in transitioning sites to new ownership.
- Coordinated content delivery for dozens of daily titles ensuring minimal service disruption.

Nickelodeon, Games Tester, San Francisco, CA

June 2008 - June 2011

- Manually tested 4-5 games per week to uncover functional and gameplay issues.
- Identified and remedied online game and site issues.
- Verification of bug fixes/regression testing.
- Tested new site features and functionality.
- Ensured a consistent user experience across all titles.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES & DATABASES: JavaScript, Python, Java, MySQL, MongoDB, GraphQL, HTML, CSS
FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: React, Node.js, Express, jQuery, Bootstrap, Materialize
OTHER SKILLS: Mac, Linux, Windows, Git, SVN, Jira, Confluence, Basecamp, Help Scout, Google Docs, MS Office, Customer Support

EDUCATION

UCLA Extension

Certificate Full Stack Web Development 2019

City College of San Francisco

Certificate Java Programming 2010

University of California, Berkeley

B.A. French 2003